<titles><title>'Rusters'.  The corrosive action of palmar sweat: I. Sodium chloride
in sweat.</title><title>Inflammatory middle ear diseases in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Precipitating antibodies against Escherichia coli, Bacteroides
fragilis ss.  thetaiotaomicron and Pseudomonas aeruginosa in serum
from normal persons and cystic fibrosis patients, determined by
means of crossed immunoelectrophoresis.</title><title>Exocrine pancreatic insufficiency, small intestinal dysfunction and
protein intolerance.  A chance occurrence or a connection?.</title><title>Increased intracranial pressure in infants with cystic fibrosis
[letter].</title><title>Precipitating antibodies against Haemophilus influenzae and
Staphylococcus aureus in sputum and serum from patients with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>IgA and IgG antibodies against surface antigens of Pseudomonas
aeruginosa in sputum and serum from patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Activated complement in the sputum from patients with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Autoantibodies in serum and sputum from patients with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Chronic obstructive lung disease.</title><title>Meconium in health and in disease.</title><title>The effect of oral zinc supplementation on plasma levels of vitamin
A and retinol-binding protein in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>The fecal microflora and bile acids in children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Serum glycine-conjugated bile acids in pediatric hepatobiliary
disorders.</title><title>Comparison of the chloride electrode and gravimetric chloride
titration sweat tests.</title><title>Comparison of the errors due to the use of gauze and the use of
filter paper in the gravimetric chloride titration sweat test.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis with acute hypoelectrolytemia and metabolic
alkalosis in infancy.</title><title>Demineralization in cystic fibrosis detected by direct photon
absorptiometry.</title><title>Psychosocial support for adults with cystic fibrosis: a group
approach.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis in adults.  75 cases and a review of 232 cases in
the literature.</title><title>Genetic counseling and prenatal diagnosis of cystic fibrosis
[letter].</title><title>Quantitative evaluation of the development of the exocrine pancreas
in cystic fibrosis and control infants.</title><title>A comparative study of inhaled atropine sulfate and isoproterenol
hydrochloride in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>The pulmonary circulation: remodeling in growth and disease.  The
1978 J. Burns Amberson lecture.</title><title>Aspergillosis and atopy in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Maximal expiratory flows after postural drainage.</title><title>Relationship between response to exercise and allergy in patients
with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Radioimmunoassay of trypsin.  A new aid in the assessment of
pancreatic function.</title><title>Endobronchial balloon tamponade of hemoptysis in patients with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Antimicrobial susceptibilities of rough, smooth, and mucoid colony
types of Pseudomonas isolated from cystic fibrosis patients.</title><title>Results of 10 years of screening of newborn infants for inherited
metabolic diseases in the province of Limburg (Belgium).</title><title>Comparative trial of manual and mechanical percussion technique with
gravity-assisted bronchial drainage in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Paediatric Research Society.  Plymouth, 15 and 16 September 1978:
Abstracts.</title><title>Screening for cystic fibrosis in the newborn by meconium analysis.</title><title>Pulmonary candidiasis in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Intestinal bile salts in cystic fibrosis: studies in the patient and
experimental animal.</title><title>Possible hazard of timed-release aspirin in a patient with
pancreatic insufficiency.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis with brain abscess.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis and hearing loss.</title><title>Vocational development and adjustment of adolescents with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Pharmacokinetics of azlocillin in children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Dying children need help too.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis: is it relevant to family practitioners?.</title><title>Inhibition of Tamm-Horsfall glycoprotein induction of alkaline
phosphatase in cystic fibrosis fibroblasts by medium conditioned by
normal cells.</title><title>Antibody responses to influenza virus vaccine in patients with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Biological activities of cystic fibrosis serum.  III.  CF serum
induced uptake of 45Ca++ by rabbit tracheal explants.</title><title>Differential concanavalin A binding of cystic fibrosis and normal
liver alpha-L-fucosidase.</title><title>Enzyme immunoassay of albumin as an aid to the diagnosis of cystic
fibrosis in the newborn human [proceedings].</title><title>Induction of alkaline phosphatase in cultured human fibroblasts.
Comparison of normal cells and those from patients with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Plasma membrane lipids of human diploid fibroblasts from normal
individuals and patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>2. Theories of genetic causation in human disease.</title><title>Bronchial artery embolization in the control of massive haemoptysis.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis in adults [editorial].</title><title>New mechanical aid to physiotherapy in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Evaluation of the forced expiration technique as an adjunct to
postural drainage in treatment of cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Dying children need help too.</title><title>Nocturnal elemental diet for retarded growth in a patient with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Lung function abnormalities in cystic fibrosis and changes during
growth.</title><title>The role of nutritional status, airway obstruction, hypoxia and
abnormalities in serum lipid composition in limiting exercise
tolerance in children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>One breath at a time: a family teaching program for children with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Noninvasive radionuclide assessment of right ventricular performance
in man.</title><title>In vitro susceptibility of pseudomonas to four
beta-lactamantibiotics (ampicillin, cephalothin, carbenicillin,
piperacillin), to four aminoglycosides (kanamycin, amikacin,
gentamicin, tobramycin) and to colimycin.</title><title>Echocardiographic profiles of the long-term cardiac changes in
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Lymphocytic acid-hydrolases and response to mitogens in cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Measurement of regional lung function by tetrapolar electrical
impedance plethysmography.</title><title>Evaluation of the single-breath diffusing capacity in asthma and
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Echocardiographic abnormalities in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Response to bronchial provocation and exercise in children with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>IgE mediated hypersensitivity to pancreatic extract (PE) in parents
of cystic fibrosis (CF) children.</title><title>A study of erythrocyte fatty acids, adenosinetriphosphatase and
acetylcholinesterase in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Measurement of 4-hydroxyphenylacetic aciduria as a screening test
for small-bowel disease.</title><title>Quality of sweat test performance in the diagnosis of cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Secretion of beta-N-acetylglucosaminidase isoenzymes by cultured
cystic fibrosis fibroblasts.</title><title>Glycosidases in serum of cystic fibrosis patients.</title><title>Carboxypeptidase B activity of cultured skin fibroblasts and
relationship to cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Decreased sialic acid and altered binding to lectins of purified
alpha 2-macroglobulin from patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Abnormal distribution of alpha-L-fucosidase in cystic fibrosis:
decreased activity in serum.</title><title>Electrolytes and norepinephrine levels in blood of patients with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Primary amniotic fluid cell, skin fibroblast and liver
alpha-L-fucosidase and its relation to cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Allergy in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Heterozygote advantage in cystic fibrosis: mosquito tests.</title><title>Deficiency of serum carboxypeptidase B-like (anaphylatoxin
inactivator, carboxypeptidase N) activity in sera from patients with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>False-positive 111In-labeled leukocyte scan in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Study of the oligosaccharide units from mucus glycoproteins of
meconium from normal infants and from cases of cystic fibrosis with
meconium ileus.</title><title>Pseudomonas aeruginosa infection: pathogenesis and therapy.</title><title>Lipids in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Obstruction of the respiratory pathways, its evaluation by methods
of functional examination of the lungs and development in patients
with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Prenatal diagnosis of cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Clinical pharmacology in a paediatric hospital.</title><title>Protease deficiency in plasma of patients with cystic fibrosis.
Reduced reaction of 4-methylumbelliferylguanidinobenzoate with
plasma of patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Evaluation of long term tobramycin therapy in patients with cystic
fibrosis and advanced pulmonary disease.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis: decreased thermostability of alpha-mannosidase in
crude extracellular fluids of patients and carriers.</title><title>Relationship between clinical conditions, radiographic findings and
pulmonary functions in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Complement in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Substance P plasma levels in pregnancy and in various clinical
disorders.</title><title>The effect of serum from patients with pancreatic disease on the
short circuit current of rat jejunum.</title><title>Defective cellular immunity to gram-negative bacteria in cystic
fibrosis patients.</title><title>High dosage tobramycin treatment of children with cystic fibrosis.
Bacteriological effect and clinical ototoxicity.</title><title>The immotile-cilia syndrome and other ciliary diseases.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Tobramycin ototoxicity.  Repeated courses of high dosage treatment
in children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Round table discussion--treatment of lower respiratory tract
infections with co-trimoxazole.</title><title>Epidemiology of cystic fibrosis: a review.</title><title>The impact of grief: a retrospective study of family function
following loss of a child with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Synthesis of hemoglobin Aic and related minor hemoglobin by
erythrocytes.  In vitro study of regulation.</title><title>Serotypes and antibiotic susceptibilities of Pseudomonas aeruginosa
isolates from single sputa of cystic fibrosis patients.</title><title>Dietary problems associated with the care of chronically sick
children.</title><title>Inborn errors of metabolism: the need for sugar.</title><title>Therapeutic possibilities in Pseudomonas infections.</title><title>Multiple of isolates of Pseudomonas aeruginosa with differing
antimicrobial susceptibility patterns from patients with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Summary of a workshop on infections in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Sulfhydryl-mediated depression of ciliary activity: an adverse
effect of acetylcysteine.</title><title>Adult cystic fibrosis: a new therapeutic challenge for the primary
care physician.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis in Northern Ireland.</title><title>Cutaneous necrotizing venulitis in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>HLA determinants in families with more than one member with cystic
fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Episodic arthritis in children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Failure to thrive, anemia, and anasarca.</title><title>Bronchial hyperreactivity in cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>A peroral test of pancreatic insufficiency with
4-(N-acetyl-L-tyrosyl)aminobenzoic acid in children with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>The effect of cimetidine on maldigestion in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Normal neutrophil and monocyte chemotaxis in patients with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Hyperuricemia in cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Bronchial artery embolization in cystic fibrosis; technique and
long-term results.</title><title>Reliability of sweat test in cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>25-Hydroxycholecalciferol levels in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Reduced serum 25-hydroxyvitamin D concentration and disordered
mineral metabolism in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Serum concentrations of 25-hydroxyvitamin D and
24,25-dihydroxyvitamin D in patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Atypical cystic fibrosis of the pancreas with normal levels of sweat
chloride and minimal pancreatic lesions.</title><title>Noninvasive evaluation of ventricular function in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Aminoglycoside clearance in patients with cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>A placebo-controlled trial of cephalexin therapy in the ambulatory
management of patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>False positive sweat test, malnutrition, and the Mauriac syndrome.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis in two black children with sickle cell anemia.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis and malnutrition.</title><title>Preatherosclerotic aortic lesions in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>PABA-test for diagnosis of exocrine pancreatic insufficiency
[letter].</title><title>Brain abscess and cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Meconium ileus: laparotomy without resection, anastomosis, or
enterostomy.</title><title>The effect of histamine, metiamide and cystic fibrosis factor on the
electrophysiological properties of the frog's gastric mucosa
[proceedings].</title><title>The chronically ligated submandibular salivary duct of the rabbit as
a possible model for cystic fibrosis [proceedings].</title><title>Sweat tests [letter].</title><title>The sweat test for cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Immunoreactive serum trypsin in diseases of the pancreas.</title><title>Differential pathology of nasal polyps in cystic fibrosis and atopy.</title><title>Sensitive trypsin assay for dried-blood specimens as a screening
procedure for early detection of cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Detection of cystic fibrosis with plasma hydrolases [letter].</title><title>Dried blood spot screening for cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Age dependence of serum angiotensin-converting enzyme activity
[letter].</title><title>Methylumbelliferyl-guanidinobenzoate reactive proteases and prenatal
diagnosis of cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Screening for cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Serum-angiotensin-converting-enzyme in chronic granulomatous disease
[letter].</title><title>Dried-blood spot screening for cystic fibrosis in the newborn.</title><title>Allergy and bronchial hyperreactivity in cystic fibrosis [editorial].</title><title>Serum-immunoreactive-trypsin concentrations in cystic fibrosis
[letter].</title><title>Methylumbelliferyl-guanidinobenzoate reactive proteases in amniotic
fluid: possible marker for cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Plasma hydrolases in cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Mechanical chest physiotherapy [editorial].</title><title>Detection of cystic fibrosis homozygotes and heterozygotes with
plasma [letter].</title><title>Arginine esterase in amniotic fluid: possible marker for cystic
fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Detection of cystic fibrosis homozygotes and heterozygotes with
plasma.</title><title>Differential incorporation of 3H-thymidine into DNA in cultured skin
fibroblasts derived from patients with cystic fibrosis and controls.</title><title>Animal model for cystic fibrosis: pulmonary clearance of
Staphylococcus aureus in mice treated with reserpine.</title><title>Increased resistance to influenza as a possible source of
heterozygote advantage in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Pathogenesis of cystic fibrosis: possible importance of alteration
in epithelial surface topography.</title><title>Alkaline phosphatase induction in cystic fibrosis fibroblasts
[letter].</title><title>Improved survival of patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Alkaline phosphatase induction in cystic fibrosis fibroblasts
[letter].</title><title>The short-term effects of chest physiotherapy on lung function tests
in children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Effect of four physiotherapy schedules on pulmonary function in
children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Relationship between clinical conditions, chest radiographic
findings and respiratory function tests in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>A new percussion aid for cystic fibrosis patients.</title><title>The mechanism of autogenic drainage studied with flow volume curves.</title><title>Intestinal lactase deficiency in newborns with cystic
fibrosis--dietary consequences.</title><title>Ultrastructure of the bronchial epithelium in children with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Recent research in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Relevance of second messengers in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Trace element malabsorption in exocrine pancreatic insufficiency.</title><title>Prostaglandins and cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Operational definition of cystic fibrosis.  I.</title><title>Alpha-glucosidase in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Postprandial total serum bile acid concentrations in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>The cystic fibrosis gene, IgE and IgG4.</title><title>Bronchial reactivity in children with cystic fibrosis and other
recurrent or chronic bronchopulmonary diseases.</title><title>Increased serum TSH response to TRH in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Factors influencing the frequency of cystic fibrosis in South West
Africa.</title><title>The effect of cystic fibrosis and non-cystic fibrosis plasma on
electrophysiological responses in isolated frog gastric mucosa.</title><title>Fatty acid supplementation in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Bronchial provocation tests in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>The local immune status in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Complement activation and pulmonary inflammation in CF patients.</title><title>Protein, IgA, secretory IgA, IgG and electrolytes as parameters of
parotid gland function in children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Precipitating antibodies against E. coli, B. fragilis, and P.
aeruginosa in CF patients and normal persons determined by means of
crossed immunoelectrophoresis.</title><title>Screening for cystic fibrosis in the newborn.</title><title>Sulphated glycoproteins in the pancreas.</title><title>An evaluation of the meconium 'lactase test' for the detection of
cystic fibrosis in the newborn.</title><title>Two children with cystic fibrosis and myocardial fibrosis.</title><title>Chemical comparison of normal and cystic fibrosis meconium: a
quantitative and qualitative analysis of carbohydrate splitting
enzymes.</title><title>The use and abuse of antibiotics, including in management of
pulmonary manifestations in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Long-term tobramycin therapy in patients with cystic fibrosis and
advanced pulmonary disease.</title><title>Bioavailability of oral antibiotics in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Progress in screening.</title><title>Diagnosing cystic fibrosis in adults [letter].</title><title>Case records of the Massachusetts General Hospital.  Weekly
clinicopathological exercises.  Case 8-1979.</title><title>Mitochondrial calcium uptake and oxygen consumption in cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis and erroneous sweat tests.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis: a disease of unknown causes.</title><title>Prone immersion physical exercise therapy in three children with
cystic fibrosis: a pilot study.</title><title>Anemia, hypoproteinemia and edema in an infant with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Serum vitamin D and related mineral metabolism in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>The pyridine scale for clinical measurement of olfactory threshold:
a quantitative reevaluation.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis in adults: an autopsy study.</title><title>Invited review.  The technique and scope of electron-probe X-ray
analysis in pathology.</title><title>Genetic aspects of pediatric lung disease.</title><title>Perspectives in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Increased heparin binding in cystic fibrosis: a reflection of
altered glycoprotein biosynthesis?.</title><title>The chronically reserpinized rat as an animal model for cystic
fibrosis: I. Acute effect of isoproterenol and pilocarpine upon
pulmonary lavage fluid.</title><title>Altered polyamine metabolism in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Chronically reserpinized rat as a model for cystic fibrosis: Na+
transport inhibitory effect in submaxillary saliva.</title><title>Evidence against a specific effect of serum from patients with
cystic fibrosis on sodium-dependent glucose transport in the rat
jejunum.</title><title>Altered intracellular calcium in fibroblasts from patients with
cystic fibrosis and heterozygotes.</title><title>Anomalous alpha 2-macroglobulin-protease complexes in cystic
fibrosis: decreased uptake of the complexes by fibroblasts in
culture.</title><title>Inhibitory effect of cystic fibrosis serum on pseudomonas
phagocytosis by rabbit and human alveolar macrophages.</title><title>Serum ciliotoxic activity in mutant mice with some hereditary
alterations resembling cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Binding of 125I-labeled proteinases to plasma proteins in cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Serum salivary amylase in cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>Development of an improved tracheal explant bioassay for the
detection of the ciliary dyskinesia factor in cystic fibrosis serum.</title><title>Laser light-scattering spectroscopy: preliminary results on bioassay
of cystic fibrosis factor(s).</title><title>Cystic fibrosis serum effect on the short circuit current of rat
jejunum.</title><title>Detection of cystic fibrosis protein by isoelectric focusing of
serum [letter].</title><title>Cystic fibrosis protein, a confirmed diagnostic marker for detecting
heterozygote carriers: significance in relation to future screening
and to a proposed primary defect in alpha 2-macroglobulin.</title><title>Serum factor in cystic fibrosis: correlation with clinical
parameters.</title><title>Intravenous linoleic acid supplementation in children with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>The chest roentgenogram in cystic fibrosis: a new scoring system.</title><title>Negative effects of oral fatty acid supplementation on sweat
chloride in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Hypoelectrolytemia and metabolic alkalosis in infants with cystic
fibrosis.</title><title>Multifocal myocardial necrosis and fibrosis in pancreatic diseases
of children.</title><title>Vitamin E: where do we stand?.</title><title>Metabolic alkalosis in infants with cystic fibrosis [letter].</title><title>An evaluation of the forced expiration technique as an adjunct to
postural drainage.</title><title>A rapid procedure for the large scale purification of elastase and
cathepsin G from human sputum.</title><title>Mitrochondrial NADH dehydrogenase in cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis: potential management through manipulation of the
secretory process in affected exocrine glands.</title><title>Changing patterns of genetic counseling in a cystic fibrosis center.</title><title>New test to detect carriers of gene for cystic fibrosis [news].</title><title>Cystic fibrosis--its surgical presentation.</title><title>Chemotherapy of chronic infections with mucoid Pseudomonas
aeruginosa in lower airways of patients with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Proteins in bronchial secretion of children with chronic pulmonary
diseases.  I. Relation to clinical diagnosis.</title><title>Proteins in bronchial secretion of children with chronic pulmonary
diseases.  II.  Relation to bronchoscopic and bronchographic
examination.</title><title>Killing of fibroblasts by dexamethasone or dibutyryl adenosine
3',5'-monophosphate is not a valid test for cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Premature senescence in cultured skin fibroblasts from subjects with
cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis in adolescents and young adults.</title><title>Implications of cystic fibrosis for health services and the
afflicted.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis: diagnosis, treatment, and prognosis.</title><title>Distal splenorenal shunt for decompression of portal hypertension in
children with cystic fibrosis.</title><title>Cystic fibrosis: review of investigations of the mucociliary
inhibitor.</title><title>"Small airways disease" in children: no test is best.</title><title>Detection of a lectin in the blood of cystic fibrosis homozygotes
and heterozygotes.</title><title>Deficiencies of essential fatty acids and vitamin E in cystic
fibrosis.</title></titles>